コードギアス反逆のルルーシュR2 TURN 14　ギアス　狩り
TURN 14　ギアス　狩り
Right now, nobody yet knows.
今はまだ　誰も知らない
ブリタニアの少年　ルルーシュの思惑とは別に
About all the many desires and heaving
emotions within the young Britannian Lelouch...
あまたの欲と感情のうねりがあることを
aside from the
expectations he has.
In that case, there is another
enemy Lelouch must confront.
ならば ルルーシュは もうひとつの敵を相手にせねばならない
しかし その相手は 見据えねばならない敵は
However, this enemy...
This enemy he must face...
is the sinful nature
of humanity itself.
まさに　人の業そのものとなる
希望と贖罪 自由と孤独
Hope and atonement.
Freedom and isolation.
だが 世界という塊は
However, the mass known
as the world...
keeps on flowing despite
the wishes of individuals.
個人の意志とは無関係に ただ流れ行くだけ
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
Kireigoto dake jaa ikirenai
Pretty words alone won't sustain you
Yasashisa dake jaa iyasenai
Kindness alone won't heal you
Ubawareta nowa nanda
What is it that was stolen from you
Kawaranai sekai de
In this unchanging world
Kikoetekita nowa nanda
What is it that you hear
Shikisai no uta
A song of color
Everything is bright...
Kudakechitta yume wo
Let our crumbled dreams resound
Asu no hate ni hibikaseru you ni
At the edge of tomorrow
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Bokura hitotsu ni
Becomes one with us
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
GEASS HUNT
シャルル 皇帝になってみて 何かわかった？
Charles, have you learned
anything by becoming emperor?
みんな うそつきばかりですよ 兄さん
That all people do is lie, big brother.
相変わらずですブリタニアという国は
That this nation of Britannia never changes.
それをいうなら 人間というのは だろ
But even saying that,
it's human nature, isn't it?
そうかもしれませんねえ
You may be right.
You won't forget, will you, Charles?
Our contract?
シャルル 忘れてないよね 僕等の契約を
わかっていますよ
I know.
To kill God and smash this world of lies...
神を殺し 世界の嘘を壊す
危なかったね 兄さん
That was a close call, big brother.
Shirley regained her memory.
シャーリーの記憶が戻っていたんだ
拳銃を手に兄さんをおいかけていたから
She had a gun
and was coming after you.
I see...
You were the one who killed her.
そうかおまえがシャーリーを
うん 兄さんの敵は僕が排除しなきゃ
Right. I have to eliminate
your enemies, big brother.
ロロ
Rolo...
何？兄さん
What, big brother?
よくやってくれた
You did well.
おまえがいなかったら 俺の秘密がみんなにばれるところだった
If it hadn't been for you,
everyone would know my secret.
だって もう兄さんだけの秘密じゃないもの
Well, after all, it isn't just
your secret anymore, big brother.
そうだな
True. So, shall we destroy
the Geass Order now?
じゃあ ギアス嚮団をぶっこわしにいくか
えっ
黒の騎士団で奇襲をかけ ギアスの源をせん滅する
We'll attack them by
surprise with the Black Knights...
and destroy the source
of Geass once and for all.
Big brother, we can't.
The Order still has Geass users there.
ダメだよ 兄さん
嚮団にはまだギアスの使い手が
逃げているだけでは明日はこない
If we just keep running away,
tomorrow will never come.
それに俺たちが幸せになるためだ
Besides, this is for our happiness.
僕たちが？
Our?
そうだV.V.はお前も疑っている
V.V. has begun
to suspect you as well.
怖いか？V.V.が
Are you afraid of V.V.?
だって 僕を拾ってくれた人だもの
After all, he was
the one who found me.
でも 兄さん 信じていいの？
Still... Big brother,
should I believe you?
あたりまえだろたった二人の兄弟じゃないか
Of course. We're the only
brothers we have, aren't we?
私を殺すか？
Are you going to kill me?
Or control me with your Geass?
それともギアスで私をあやつるか？
ユフィのように
Like Euphy?
妹の無実をはらすために位を捨て
To prove your sister's innocence,
you abandoned your position and the military.
軍を捨て すてきだよね
That's wonderful.
I've been thinking.
僕は思うんだ
きょうだいってこの世界でもっとも美しい関係なんじゃないかって
Is there any more wonderful relationship
in this world than that of siblings?
銃創と出血による多臓器不全です
Multiple organ failure due to
gunshot wounds and loss of blood.
シャーりーが 自分で自分を撃ったと？
Shirley... You're saying she shot herself?
はい 発作的な
Yes. On a sudden impulse.
いや～～あ
シャーリー
シャーリーが 自殺
Shirley committed suicide?
So... Any sign of Lelouch?
ねえ ルルーシュは？
Holy Britannian Empire
DALLAS RESEARCH CENTER
そう 友達が
はいミレイさんから連絡が
I see. A friend of yours.
Yeah. Milly contacted me about it.
仲よかったの？
Were you close?
I'm not sure...
She was always so cheerful.
さあ とても明るい子で
正直私苦手でした
To be honest,
she sort of bugged me.
羨ましかったんじゃない？その子のこと
Maybe because
you were jealous of her?
たぶん そうなんでしょうね
Maybe... Maybe that was it.
That was it...
だって だって涙が出るなんて思わなかった
I never thought
I would cry over her!
ニーナ涙が流せるうちは　大丈夫
Nina...
There's nothing wrong
with shedding a few tears.
United States of Japan
Provisional Capital - HORAI ISLAND
まったくルルーシュのやつ
この私をなんだと思ってるんだ
For heaven's sake, Lelouch. Who does he think I am?
伝言係としてほったらかしにしたままで
Just leaving me behind
like I'm some kind of messenger.
What?!
はあ？まさか 契約を忘れていないか心配なだけだ
Hardly. I'm just worrying
that he's forgotten our contract.
Anyway, what are you planning to do?
How long are you...
それより おまえこそどうする気だ？
いつまでも
C.C.
ん？
ジェレミアのロロの協力で嚮団の位置は特定できた
I've been able to locate the Order
with Jeremiah and Rolo's assistance.
零番隊を投入し 嚮団をいっきにせん滅する
We're going to send in Zero
Squad and wipe it out in one blow.
Wipe it out?
Weren't you going to use it?
せん滅？
利用するんじゃなかったのか？
あれは武装組織ではなく ギアスを研究するだけの
They're not an armed group.
They just do Geass research...
せん滅だ！
We're wiping them out!
何があった？
What happened?
シャーリーは 最後までギアスに翻弄されて
To the very end, the power of
Geass made sport with Shirley.
Shirley was killed by Geass!
シャーリーはギアスに殺されたんだ
And so now you're going to wipe out the Order?
だから嚮団を消すのか？
同じ悲劇をくりかえさないために
As atonement? So that the
same tragedy isn't repeated?
贖罪として
これが王の力だというのなら
If this truly is the power of the king,
then I'm the only one who needs to have it!
力あるものはひとりで十分だ
ロロはもちろん ギアスという力 罪
Not only Rolo!
I'll erase the power called Geass,
its sins, and its very existence
from this world!
存在そのものをこの世界から消してやる！
シャーリーに対して それがせめてもの
I owe Shirley that much, at least!
では 私も消すか？
Then are you going to erase me, as well?
消したくとも消せないだろうな
I couldn't even if I wanted to,
you eternally young immortal witch!
不老不死の魔女め
不老不死という点では V.V.も同じだが
V.V. is just as eternally young
and immortal, you know.
活動できなくすればいい
Neutralizing his activities is good enough.
There's always the method
Clovis once used on you.
かつてクロヴィスがとった方法だってある
それより お前が俺に協力するかしないのか確認したい
Besides, I want to confirm whether
you're cooperating with me or not.
一応嚮団のトップだったんだろ
You were once director
of the Order, after all.
昔のことだ
That was a long time ago. And I was
just window dressing. Nothing like V.V.
それに 私はただのお飾り
V.V.とは違う
しかし おまえと私は共犯者だったな
However...
We've been accomplices, haven't we?
情けは邪魔になる作戦だが？
There's no room for
sympathy on this mission.
最後を看取る覚悟はあるよ
I'm prepared to see
this through to the end.
では もう一つ確認したい
Then there's one other thing I'd like to be sure of.
The details of our contract.
俺との契約内容を
お前の願いはなんだ？
What is it you want?
作戦には関係ないだろう
That has nothing to do with the mission,
does it? I've no intention of telling you now.
今話すつもりはない
Hmpf! Selfish woman!
ふんわがままな女だ
そうとも私はC.C.なのだから
Exactly. That's what makes me C.C.
バトレーたちはまだしも
Bartley and the others are one thing,
but what do we do about Princess Cornelia?
コーネリア皇女殿下はどうなさるのですか？
せめて　皇帝陛下に 連絡だけでも
Shouldn't we at least
contact His Majesty?
う～ん
Hm...
シャルルはコーネリアの動きを知っていたのかな？
I wonder if Charles knew about
Cornelia's actions. Or if he didn't...
知らなかったのかな？
は？
What?
嚮主V．V． ジェレミア卿より定時連絡です
Director V.V., we have a scheduled
report from Lord Jeremiah.
ああ ここにつないで
Right. Patch it through.
はじめまして
How do you do?
おまえがV.V.か
So, you're V.V.?
ルルーシュ
Lelouch!
なぜジェレミアの通信ネットワークを
How can he have access to
Jeremiah's communication network?!
Where's the signal originating from?
発信元は？
エリア11 アッシュフォード学園内かと
Area 11, from inside Ashford Academy, I think.
今さら自己紹介は必要ないだろう
I'm sure I need no introduction at this point.
そのうえでききたいことがある
That said, there's something
I'd like to ask you.
トウキョウ決戦のとき ナナリーをさらったのはおまえか？
Was it you who kidnapped Nunnally
during the battle for Tokyo?
神根島に俺やスザクたちを集め
Did you put Suzaku and I and the
others on Kamine Island to observe us?
観察者をきどっていたのも
Yes, that's correct.
うん そうだよ
But the fact you're asking that question means
you've regained your memories, doesn't it?
でもそれをきくということは
やっぱり記憶は戻っていたんだね
ああ俺がゼロだ
Yes, I am Zero.
じゃあ C.C.もいっしょなんでしょ
Then C.C. must be with you, correct?
Will you hand her over?
C.C.をちょうだい
そうすれば君は自由に
We'll let you go free if you do.
もう遅い！すでにこれは俺とおまえとの戦争となった
It's too late for that!
I'm already at war with you people!
ふ～んでも君がここに来るころには僕たちはもう次の場所に
Oh?
However, by the time you get here,
we'll already have moved to another place...
嚮主V．V．！ナイトメアが！
Director V.V.! Knightmares!
何？
What?!
黒の騎士団と思われます
I think it's the Black Knights!
V.V.の現在位置は特定できた
V.V.'s current location has been verified.
全軍ポイントアルファ７を包囲とC.C.
All forces, encircle point alpha-7!
なるほど そういうことかい
I see. So, that's how it is.
ああ 少しの時間でよかった
Yes. I'm glad you gave me a bit of your time.
I just needed you to let down
your guard for a moment.
ほんの少しだけおまえが油断すれば
俺がまだエリア１１にいると思いこみ
Making you think I was still in Area 11 made
you think you still had time to escape.
脱出する時間が少し遅れるだけで
V.V. 裁きを下すのは 俺だ
V.V., the one who shall
render judgment here is I!
イジェクトダートに研究データを運び入れて
Load our research data into the Eject Dart.
And prep the weapon for my use.
それと僕にはあれの用意を
Wha?! Director,
you're facing them personally?
嚮主様 御自ら
脱出の時間をかせがないと
I need to buy you time to escape.
それにしつけが必要だよ
Besides, I have to
discipline Marianne's child.
マリアンヌの子どもには
まさかねえ
I never would have guessed.
ナナリーがお姫様だったなんてねえ
That you were a princess, Nunnally.
嘘をついていてごめんなさい
Forgive me for lying to you.
お互いさまよ
Same from me.
懐かしいですアッシュフォード学園のこと
It's so nostalgic,
talking about Ashford Academy.
ミレイさんたちには言わないようにと言われているので
They told me I wasn't
to see Milly and the others,
おはなしできるのがスザクさんしか
so Suzaku is the only one
I've been able to talk to.
お兄様も 行方知れずということですし
They also tell me that my big
brother is nowhere to be found.
ルルーシュって どんなお兄さんだったの？
What sort of brother
was Lelouch to you?
え
私にもね お兄ちゃんがいたのだから
I used to have
a big brother, too, so...
嬉しいですお兄様のお話ができるなんて
I'm happy. Just to be able
to talk about him...
失礼します
Excuse me.
ナナリー総督
Viceroy Nunnally, I'd like to
borrow prisoner 1-0-7 from you.
捕虜107号をおかりしたいのですが
木下副隊長 何か変です
Sub-commander Kinoshita,
something's wrong here!
ここはほんとにブリタニア軍の施設なんですか
Is this really a Britannian
military installation?
た 確かに 反撃がひとつもない
Y-You're right.
There hasn't been any resistance at all.
Everyone here is completely unarmed!
ここにいるのは 武装していない連中ばかりだ
疑わしきは罰せよ！
No one here is to be
considered innocent!
でも
But!
Britannia has been colluding with
traitors in the Chinese Federation.
ブリタニアは 中華連邦の内通者と結託し
この場所で死なない兵士を研究 実験している
They're doing research and
experimentation on immortal soldiers here!
そのような生命の冒涜を許してはならない！
I will not allow these abominations to live!
研究員やデータはすべて抹消する
The researchers and their data are to be wiped out!
We don't know where they have
their experimental subjects hidden!
どこに実験体がひそんでいるかわからぬ
ゆえに ポイントアルファ７を包囲しつつ
Therefore, encircle point alpha-7!
すべてを破壊し 焼き尽くせ！
Destroy everything!
Burn it to the ground!
実験体とおぼしき者を発見し次第
Any possible experimental subjects found are
all to be sealed inside the high pressure case!
高圧ケースにすべて封印せよ！
私が直々に検証する
I will verify them myself!
コーネリア皇女殿下はまだみつからんのか？
Haven't you found Princess Cornelia yet?!
この隙にお救いせねば
We have to use this chance to save...
あの男 たしか クロヴィスといっしょにいた
That man...
Wasn't he working with Clovis?
Lady C.C.!
C.C.様！！戻ってこられたのですね
You've come back to us!
Please save us, Lady C.C.!
お助けください　C.C.様！
Prince Clovis...
ク クロヴィス殿下
皇帝陛下に献上しようとした不老不死の女ですが
The eternally young and immortal woman
you wished to present to His Majesty...
すでに 陛下はその存在をご存じだったようです
It would seem he already
knew of her existence.
P- Please forgive me...
も　申し訳ありません　かかわらねばよかった あんな 女
We should never have
involved ourselves with her...
はい ゼロはブリタニアの研究施設をたたくと
Yes, Zero said he's gone to attack
a Britannian research facility.
しかし 場所や作戦内容までは
However, he's kept the
location and mission a secret.
More clandestine activities?
また極秘行動か
サウジの平定もすんだ今 合衆国憲章の批准を急がねばならぬのだが
Now that the Saudis
have been subjugated,
we have to hurry up and
ratify the united states charter.
たしかに ブリタニアの脅しに屈する勢力はふえつつありますからね
More and more nations are
falling to the Britannian menace.
しかしイタリアやポーランドはこちらの味方となった
However, Poland and Italy
are now on our side.
ゼロが戻り次第連絡を頼む
Contact us as soon as Zero returns.
わかりました
Understood.
ということでよいのだな
This is what Zero wants, right?
はい ゼロの行動 存在について機密は守られねばなりません
Right. We have to maintain secrecy
around Zero's activities and his existence.
ならば君には 扇副指令をおってもらおう
Then I want you to go after
Deputy Commander Ohgi.
え
先日の会議から 扇副指令がおかしい
He's been acting strangely since
the meeting a few days ago.
いや それ以前から彼は何かを隠している
No... He's been hiding something
for a long time before that.
Area 11 - KANAZAWA AIRPORT
あ～今中華連邦への便は
私の所属は機密情報局だ
Hm... Flights to the Chinese Federation right now are...
I belong to the Office of Secret Intelligence.
こっ 皇帝陛下直属機関の
The... The one that reports directly to His Majesty?!
ああ 外交ルートによる特別便があったはずだが
Right. I believe you have special
flights for diplomatic purposes.
わかりました
I understand.
ジェレミアまでルルーシュに取り込まれた以上
Now that Lelouch has even
roped Jeremiah into this...
ゼロのためにも副指令が敵に内通しているようであれば
For Zero's sake, if the deputy commander
is collaborating with the enemy, then...
扇　要を
I must kill Kaname Ohgi!
どうしてこんなところに子どもが？
What are children doing here?
な なんだ？
Wh-What the?!
手 手が ！
My... My hand!
も 森 おまえ
M- Mori, what are you?!
違う！俺じゃない！
No! It's not me!
あっギアス
Wha? Geass?
この力って
That power means it's...
ロロお兄ちゃん
Brother Rolo?
ああ 元気にしてましたか？
Yeah. Have you been well?
新入り ロロとか言ったか
New guy... Your name's Rolo, right?
You're one of them?
おまえもここの
もう関係はありません
I have nothing to do with them now.
僕は兄さんについていきさえすれば
Not as long as I can be
with my big brother.
ふふふふふっV.V.を追い詰めた以上
Once he corners V.V., I just have to
detonate the bomb I planted in Rolo's unit.
あとはロロの機体に仕掛けた爆弾を作動させるだけ
シャーリーへの弔いとして ロロの命をささげる
My funeral offering to Shirley will
be Rolo's life! He will atone for it!
償わせてやる！
何？！
What?!
ジークフリート！
The Siegfried!
バカな
Impossible!
Jeremiah! Isn't that unit?!
ジェレミア！確かこの機体は
はい神経電位接続ですから
Right. Since it works via direct
electrical nerve connection,
私以外に動かせるものは
the only person besides me who can use it is!
ふん
やはり！
I thought so!
意外だな V.V.！
You surprise me, V.V.!
The observer becomes
the perpetrator!
観察者が　当事者になるとは！
少しは 好きだったんだけどね ルルーシュ
I sort of liked you, Lelouch.
君はシャルルに似ているから
Because you remind me of Charles.
よりによって ここでジークフリートとは！
He's using the Siegfried of all things, here?!
さがっていろ！やつの狙いはお前だ！
Get out of here!
It's you he's after!
Oh?
そこまでだ V.V.
Hold it right there, V.V.!
もう降伏してください
Please, just surrender.
何を言っているんだい？裏切り者たちが
What do you think you're saying?
Traitors!
V.Vおまえをそこからひきずりだす
V.V., I'll tear you out of that thing!
全軍 攻撃開始！
All forces, commence attack!
Yes, Your Majesty!
イエス　ユアマジェスティ！
ちっ電磁装甲は健在か
Dammit! That electromagnetic
shielding's holding up well!
マリアンヌの子どもが調子にのっても
Marianne's son may be getting carried away!
それはわが忠義のためにあるべき機体だ！
That machine was made
to let me show my loyalty!
Jeremiah, I thought you hated Zero.
ジェレミア 君はゼロを恨んでいたよね
しかり
I did! I thought he'd denied
me the ability to do my duty.
これで皇族への忠義もはたせなくなったと考えたからな
されどつかえるべきあるじがゼロであったなら
But when I learned who he was,
I saw I should serve him, for Lady Marianne's sake!
マリアンヌ様のためにも！
お前まで　その名を口にするか！
Even you!
You dare speak that name in front of me?!
残っている機体をすべて出せ
Send out all remaining units!
外にいる化け物に ここのトップがのりこんでいるらしい
It looks like that monster outside
is being piloted by their director.
シャーリーが？
Shirley?!
鑑識は 自殺だと言っている
The medical examiner
ruled it a suicide.
そんな子じゃないわ！
She'd never do that.
Suzaku, you know that, don't you?!
スザク あんただって知ってるでしょ
Yeah, I do. Which means
if someone murdered her...
ああだから彼女を殺した犯人がいるとすれば
はっ
そう ルルーシュだ
Right. It was Lelouch.
くっロロ なんとかジークフリートにとりつけないか
Rolo! Can you grab onto
the Siegfried somehow?
でも V.V.相手じゃ ギアスはきかないし
But I can't use my Geass on V.V.
You just have to grab onto him.
I have a plan after you do that.
とりつくだけでいいんだ
あとの策はある
うん やってみる
Okay, I'll try.
ロロ ここでジークフリートもろとも始末してあげよう
Rolo...
I'll finish you off with the Siegfried.
ヴィンセントに仕掛けた爆弾で
With the bomb I planted on the Vincent!
やってみせる！兄さんのためにも！
I have to try!
For big brother's sake!
今度はロロかな
And now it's Rolo.
You've lied to me too, haven't you?
君も僕に嘘をついたんだね
僕にギアスはきかないってしっているくせに
Even knowing your
Geass won't work on me...
へえ
Ah!
嚮主V．V．脱出準備が整いました
Director V.V.,
we've finished preparations to escape.
Shall we head to
the E.U. area for now?
ひとまずEU方面でよろしいでしょうか
うんこっちを片付けたら合流するよ
Right. I'll rendezvous with you
after I've finished things here.
これでC.C.をつかまえる方法ははっきりしたし
It's clear how to capture C.C. now.
ここさえ逃げれば 僕とシャルルの勝ちだね
If we escape, then Charles and I win.
とりつくだけなら！
I just have to grab on!
You're a failed project, aren't you?
君はね 失敗作だったんだよ
ギアスを使っている間 自分の心臓もとまってしまうんだって
After all, your heart stops
when you use your Geass.
いつ死んでもおかしくない欠陥品さ
You're a defective experiment
we expected to die at any moment!
まだ パージすれば
Not yet!
If I jettison them, then!
へ
Oh?
I've done it, big brother!
できたよ 兄さん！
よくやってくれたロロ
Well done, Rolo!
Now I must bid you farewell.
では ここでおまえと
え誰だい？ジークフリートの弱点を知っている攻撃
Who? Who could know to attack
the Siegfried's weak point?
V.V.といったか？
So, your name is V.V.?
この私を脆弱にして惰弱とあなどったな
By thinking I was helpless,
you underestimated me!
ごめんなさい兄さん
Forgive me, Big Brother!
いや 気にするな
No, don't worry about it.
まさか コーネリアがここにいようとは
I never expected Cornelia to be here!
ジークフリートの装甲は破損した
The Siegfried's shields are down!
Now, we just need to hit it directly!
あとは直接
くっ うう
ユフィのかたき そこで滅せよ
For Euphy's vengeance,
you shall perish here!
ギアスの
The source...
源
- ...of Geass itself!
ダメだ このジークフリートはもう くっ
It... It's no use!
The Siegfried is finished!
ルルーシュこののろわれた皇子め！
Lelouch! You accursed prince!
あっ
皇女殿下
Your Highness!
ジークフリードが
The Siegfried!
嚮主V．V．
Director V.V.!
おちつけ嚮主V．V．は朽ちることのないおからだ
Calm down!
Director V.V. cannot be killed.
最下層にある黄昏の扉もつかえるはず
He can always use the
Twilight Gate on the lowest level.
この場は我らだけでも 研究データとともに
If we just get the research data
away from here, then...
まさか！シ C.C.様！
Is that?!
Lady C.C.!
すまないこれはお前達を放置した私の罪だ
Forgive me. This is my sin
for having neglected you all.
だから ギアスの系譜はここでおわらせる
And so now I shall end
the lineage of Geass here.
それが おそらく私とルルーシュの
Perhaps...
This is the way Lelouch and I...
全ての証拠が 証言が
All of the evidence and testimony
show Lelouch to be innocent.
ルルーシュはシロだといっている
でも 僕の心はずっと ルルーシュが犯人だと
But in my heart, I've known that Lelouch
was the the culprit, that he was Zero.
ゼロであると
ゼロの正体は知らない捕まった時に言ったでしょ
I don't know Zero's true identity.
I told you that when I was captured.
Enough of that!
もういいんだ
これ以上悲劇を生みださないためにも
There's no method left I won't use to
prevent any more of these tragedies!
手段にこだわってはいられない
だからこのリフレインで
That's why I'm going
to use this Refrain...
ターゲットは施設内に逃げ込んだ
The target has fled into the facility!
私は最下層から調べ上げる
I'll look for him, starting on the lowest
level! Rolo, search from the highest!
ロロは上層から捜索
木下は部隊を率いて中層区画をあらいだせ！
Kinoshita! Take command and
sweep the middle level areas!
あぁ くっルルーシュ よくも
Lelouch... How dare you!
よくきてくれたね シャルル
I'm glad you came, Charles.
やっぱり最後に頼りになるのは兄弟だね
In the end, siblings are all
you can count on, huh?
兄さん ルルーシュに刺客を送ったというのは本当ですか？
Big brother, is it true you were the one
who sent the assassin after Lelouch?
おかげで仕返しされちゃた
And thanks to that,
I've paid a price.
ははっ でも ルルーシュがゼロだってわかったよ
Still, I learned that Lelouch is Zero.
ナナリーもだましていたんだ あいつは
He's even tricked Nunnally as well.
兄さんはまた 嘘をついた
You lied to me again, big brother.
これじゃブリタニアと同じじゃないか
This is as bad as anything
the Britannians do!
子どもまで殺す必要があったのか 本当に
Was it really necessary
to kill children as well?
ん？ここで生体反応？
I'm picking up life signs. Have you
returned to your original point, V.V.?
元のポイントに戻っていたか
何！？しまった！これは神根島の！
What?! Dammit!
This is the same as on Kamine Island!
お 俺はいつ蜃気楼から
When did I get out of the Shinkirō?
And where am I? It isn't a hologram.
それにここは？
ホログラムとかじゃない？
そのとおり
Correct!
そしてナイトメアなど無粋なもの
And Knightmares
are such inelegant things.
アーカーシャの剣 このシステムの前にはな
Especially in the face of this system:
the Sword of Akasha!
貴様 ！
You!
Lelouch, my son!
The time has come at last!
我が息子　ルルーシュよ
時は来た
あがないの時が
The time for redemption!
Dakuse wa oni
This corrupt world is filled with demons
Seigi wa nanzo to
What is justice?
Tou mae ni aragae yo
Resist, don't just question
Akutoku no hana
The flower of evil
Gizen no yume
Dreams of hypocrisy
Mishi me niwa me wo sashi
Give your gaze to the eyes that see them
Sei mo ja mo wakatareru koto nashi
The line between right and wrong cannot be known
Hikari wa tae taiji no you ni
Light is gone, and you slumber
Kimi wa nemuru yami no shikyuu
Like an unborn child in the womb of darkness
Kodoku koso itooshii
Isolation is what you love
Yui-itsu no mikata to naru darou
It will probably be your only ally
Hitori hitori chishio ni mamire
One by one, stained with the tide of blood
Kono jidai ni umare ochita
You were born into this era
Erabareshi oujira yo
Oh, chosen princes
Tatakai koso shukuen
Battle shall be your banquet
Aa ware wa uruwashii zenchi
Oh, I am graceful omniscience
Ai no haha
The loving mother
Kimi wo umu
Who bore you
Kono chichi ni hagukumishi mono wa
The ones who were raised on my breast
Jigoku no harakara
Are your brethren in hell
Mokushi no in
The mark of apocalypse
Shinri wa nanzo to
What is truth
Shirimosezu uzumoreshi intoku no tane
A seed of secrecy buried where no one knows
Moroha no ken
A double-edged sword
Nuku ha niwa ha wo muke
Turn its blade upon the unsheathed blade
Mamorubeki mono dake wo shinjite
Believe only in what you must protect
Aru ga mama ni kimi wa
And in your own way
Kimi wo hanate
You'll set yourself free
なぜ皇帝が目の前に
Why is the emperor
right in front of me?!
最善の策は俺のギアスであいつを下部とすること
Dammit, I have to reconsider the situation.
だが　あいつのギアスが　そしてこの場所が障害だ
He must be doing this because
he knows that I'm Zero.
I have no reason to hide it anymore!
何か手はないのか
The best plan would be to use my
Geass to make him my servant.
乾坤一擲　この千載一遇のチャンスを
That eliminates the need to capture
V.V. and trade him for Nunnally, but...
But his own Geass and
this place stand in my way!
Don't I have any options?!
It's all or nothing now! I have to
take this once in a lifetime chance!
THE Cs' WORLD